Guide to the Backus Historical Society Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Library, Series V
  - Collected papers
    - Joseph Grafton, Autobiographical statement, 1833 June 9 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Summons for Zattu? Pickens to appear before Isaac Stearns, justice of the peace Plymouth County, 1833 June 12 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Isabella M. Snow to [J. Grafton]; from Millbury, MA, 1833 December 30 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - History of Baptist church in Belchertown, MA (date is last dated entry), 1837 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - History of Baptist church of Wilbraham and Monson, MA (date is last dated entry), 1839 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Letter of recommendation for Horatio Lilley, 1859? September 20 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Annual letter of Boston First Baptist Mariners Church to Boston North Association, 1861 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Fragile originals; copies filed in chronological order (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Added Material, Series VI
  - Newspaper articles about Backus Historical Society, 1853–1907 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - The Backus Family: A Genealogical Memoir, 1890 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Metal illustration plate - Isaac Backus (Box 3, Folder 27)